

Lakisha Adu

- <u> lakishaadu@yahoo.de</u>
- im linkedin.com/in/lakisha-adu/
- github.com/lakishaadu

I am an analytics-oriented marketer with recent experience from a 15-week analytics bootcamp. I love applying my new knowledge and contributing to the success of campaigns. I have a high level of comprehension and am a quick learner. Managing multiple projects with tight deadlines is no problem for me.

Work experience

Organized and planned events.

Marketing Manager | JITpay Group
 11/2022 - 03/2023
 Managed marketing for customer & employee acquisition.

Content-Marketing Manager | KUPPER IT GmbH

• 04/2022 - 09/2022

Developed content for marketing materials. Planned and implemented content strategies to increase brand awareness, drive traffic, and generate leads.

Marketing & Support | Wehner Consulting GmbH

• 04/2020 - 10/2021

Developed B2B sales marketing activities; Focused on sales and lead generation, consistently driving revenue growth and customer acquisition;

Seminarmanager | MST Group GmbH

o 05/2018 - 08/2020

Planned and coordinated seminars for personnel development at the BMW Training Center and MAN;

Event Manager | Seminarcenter IM EINKLANG

• 07/2017 - 04/2018

Maintained the Home and Facebook pages; Managed Meta Ads and Marketing Campaign; Conceptualized creative event concepts;

Soft Skills & Languages

Soft Skills

Hands-on Person Analytic thinker Problem solving Communication Skills

Language

English: B2 Spanish: A1 German: Native

Education

- Marketing Analytics | WBS Coding School, Berlin Since 04/2023 - 08/2023 | Hybrid Further Education
 Focus: Tracking, Measurement, Analysis, Reporting;
- Communication & Event Management | IST Hochschule f. Management, Düsseldorf Since 04/2021 - today | Bachelor of Arts | Part-time
 Focus: Brand Management, Business Administration;
- Event Manager | IST Studieninstitut, Düsseldorf
 02/2019 02/2021 | Hybrid Further Education | Part-time
 Focus: Venue Selection and Logistics, Event Production;
- Event Manager | TNC Group GmbH, Leipzig
 09/2014 06/2017 | Apprenticeship
 Focus: Project Management, Promotion, Social Media;

Tech Skills & Knowledge

Digital Marketing

Digital Marketing Fundamentals Google Tag Manager | Google Analytics Hotjar (Heatmap and user behavior analysis)

Web Development

HTML | CSS | JavaScript (Frontend)
SQL (Database query language)
BigQuery (Data warehouse and analytics)

Conversion Optimization:

A/B Testing (For conversion rate optimization) Looker Studio (Data visualization & analytics) Web Usability & Conversion-Centered Design

Graphic Design:

Canva (Graphic design) Photoshop (Image editing)